{"cards":[{"mId":"19cb02ca-5655-4a82-a271-ada0a46c2850","mCardType":"text","mFront":"The air, water and land in or on which people, animals and plants live","mBack":"The Environment"},{"mId":"56ae169f-8ac7-406c-9f35-6faf23697c07","mCardType":"text","mFront":"The weather conditions generally present in an area or over a long period","mBack":"Climate"},{"mId":"62a5f011-1200-49e3-8bf0-0441591fa17b","mCardType":"text","mFront":"The change in global climate patterns which appeared from the mid to late 20th century onwards, caused mainly by the increased levels of carbon dioxide in the atmosphere","mBack":"Climate Change"},{"mId":"9d17c3ae-df12-470d-8fde-fec272faf9bd","mCardType":"text","mFront":"The gas formed when carbon is burned, or when people or animals breathe out","mBack":"Carbon Dioxide"},{"mId":"4cd9e510-aa27-4642-b0fd-d730b80ecb60","mCardType":"text","mFront":"A natural fuel such as coal, gas, or oil formed in the geological past from the remains of living organisms","mBack":"Fossil Fuels"},{"mId":"f382511d-4491-46d5-a75c-f22565942737","mCardType":"text","mFront":"A gradual rise in the world\u0027s temperatures caused by polluting gases such as carbon dioxide which are collecting in the air around the Earth and preventing heat escaping into space","mBack":"Global Warming"},{"mId":"01de56df-47b8-432e-8c9d-272dcfa5f042","mCardType":"text","mFront":"Cutting down and clearing areas of forest","mBack":"Deforestation"},{"mId":"574e23a3-502d-4551-b646-49501efc6b6a","mCardType":"text","mFront":"The natural environment in which an animal or plant usually lives","mBack":"Habitat"},{"mId":"0121307d-ac28-4197-8958-c4e315409bfd","mCardType":"text","mFront":"All the living things in an area and the way they affect each other and the environment","mBack":"Ecosystem"},{"mId":"39043d02-042e-49f9-b0bb-049f4b660490","mCardType":"text","mFront":"The variety of plant and animal life in the world or in a particular habitat, a high level of which is usually considered to be important and desirable","mBack":"Biodiversity"},{"mId":"bd448247-e22d-43a6-a041-536f642c5a99","mCardType":"text","mFront":"To make something less pure by exposing it to poisonous or polluting substances","mBack":"Contamination"},{"mId":"494d7c94-c019-4de5-a920-fb91afc89242","mCardType":"text","mFront":"Poisonous / A poisonous substance","mBack":"Toxic"},{"mId":"4b34475a-6aca-43dc-82f2-cee8538d35d7","mCardType":"text","mFront":"A material or substance which is eliminated or discarded as no longer useful or required after the completion of a process","mBack":"Waste"},{"mId":"b31b6965-cdb6-409f-bb14-2066688bf848","mCardType":"text","mFront":"The production and discharge of something","mBack":"Emission"},{"mId":"177abcb1-b863-4dfc-aa3c-8da2d74e402c","mCardType":"text","mFront":"To graually reduce or destroy","mBack":"Erosion"},{"mId":"5e5985ff-e5cf-44e0-88fb-1c56da3e34b2","mCardType":"text","mFront":"A prolonged period of abnormally low rainfall, leading to a shortage of water","mBack":"Drought"},{"mId":"2f5fbaed-bae8-456a-aa0d-22736d2741b4","mCardType":"text","mFront":"Damage caused to water, air, land etc. by harmful substances or waste","mBack":"Pollution"},{"mId":"839d099c-edb7-47e1-ad3d-b1321ba64469","mCardType":"text","mFront":"Causing little or no damage to the environment and therefore able to continue for a long time","mBack":"Sustainable"}]}